All the viewers should be given this video which is being
played for comedy and is being entertained
so this video is being played for fun and is being played for fun
and is
cleanly 18 plus
you can do business
you can also watch Ghar
Giri Phatan bhi
you can do kukut
bhi kaun bahar bahar
[Music]
Wow
beautiful song
[Music]
Hello guys you don't want to believe me that my
song is being played for all of us brother kiba na ki
husband na mu se fishing topic kachi which is going
viral in all India and is going viral because it is very
awesome so you should also believe me that day by day the game is being played for all the people in the country like
helicopter, snow
machine and robot machine astila and every day
lakhs of people are playing this game in India which is very popular
and they can also get their secret and you can also get
special reward in the middle of the
comment link by clicking on the above link you can pubg to daily
ki jaldi j link comment pin jaldi j
register karu and reward pantu and chah
aagey din to sab bane
[laughter]
na
hoon
Shlok me Shlok
go
to
[laughs]
where is the
property Pak
Surbaj
[laughs]
then how come sa ko
mar de [laughs]
leg to leg
to
blouse
kaarigar [laughs]
look
or
infectioncha
khacha
[music]
oka
[music
] ko o pari [
music] ko o ko o pari
[music] ye ko bari kone go hi hi hi hi [music] hi hi hi oka
[music] ko
[music]
oh pari
ko
[music]
given
ok
[laughs]
money
bar
delay
jo
bar jacha kaam si
hey
work do complete half do
[music]
uncle
home
work home
hey no work
ok brother in law go
time re yes
ok
hey Kalib
[laughs]
quickly quickly quickly inconvenience inconvenience
convenience
hurry
uncle [music]
no work at work
[laughs]
you
hurry up [laughs]
okay three work quickly give me next day
sir sir daily delay
[music]
ok
you
not today uncle tell me abba jaan take
medical abba jaan give
[laughs] no
work
troubled
money work work
quickly work
quickly work [laughs]
10 minutes  ₹
yes okay okay okay do it, after
refusing I have come I have come
the next day
Limbuda Limbuda Limbuda oh
raw raw small
Limbuda bring me [screaming voice] oh I have
brought it, I have brought it,
now
beautiful
tightening
ok Babu time is
duty ok okay do
n't be late for an hour
tailor don't cheat me don't
bother me [laughs]
uncle
[laughs]
oh ho
uncle
so uncle lie down I also lie down this is the same
story ok
uncle
you
[music]
now what [laughs]
bastard [laughter] the
world is stolen [
laughter]
daughter water elephant fat
daughter water elephant fat [music]
valley
all day
[laughter]
inconvenience
inconvenience dress
[laughter]
look
day inconvenience
inconvenience hey bastard I am
giving
my drama
Ashish Champati
Ashish Champati Ashish Champati yes sir sir your
chest is 46
chest 46 ok
arms 33 long long 35
long 35 everything is fine
colour P
Ashish Champati Ashish Champati
ok sir you do
n't
look at anything else  [laughs]
no
[laughs]
okay inconvenience
hey babu
daughter
o
aapdha bad
beard big
belly big you
gandi you
gandi mar
language
gandi mar sir sir sir
okay sir you
ready
cup [laughs]
[laughs]
hey jo dps kaam kare
[laughs] hey money
madam
blouse
saree kaam
hey madam to
ok then
stitch kare sasuri
[music]
bagwa
[laughs]
madam katha ki trailer rules
jo
kaam
[laughs]
no madam
madam
who hey madam
madam ko
achha madam
aap
suni bath
radish [laughs]
thick achha
una achha dukaan madam achha dukaan develop kar
worry kar pani sara daba daba develop karta [
laughs]
kutamin
slowly slowly slowly growth ok
vitamin
party slowly slowly slowly
no madam madam madam madam madam madam madam
you jaan
customer jaan listen listen le le le chest chest si
achha
chest [music]
karaati
chest chest
[laughs]
baby
[music] so
Instagram bahut viral ja so disgusting achha to ok khani
tu khan on
Monu tu khan
You Khan on you
see
Nagu ji you
Prem fame Swami
nahi
[laughs]
ko
[laughs] no
okay
[laughs]
de
pre voting nahi jo fatafat video ke
jikwa
[laughs]
Goa oh so very good Goa
good milab
ho poora man inner kar
inner ok inner
[laughs]
okay
so
P Mani
Khan you doubt man ko
see
madam up
[laughs]
[music]
example
[laughs]
smuggling
immigration
din bhala customer
ye market
jo kaam ya
kaam 3
[laughs]
[music]
moras
hos
[music]
cloth
you tabadi
[laughs]
so see
[laughter] okay
cloth press
press cloth keep it
good
three days
expectation
30 minutes
[laughter]
experience not very experience
okay okay
30 minutes
Babu
ki Babu accha apan to
Goa jaaun
char five days jaaun
four five days
oh 15 days hotel booking accha
din jaa na so
you
cloth cloth
[laughs] you  No, you
gave the clothes, gave the
clothes, I only
saw
madam
[laughter]
Babu, you are
empty of the goods, only looking at the customers
[laughter], are
you done with the
inconvenience of Radhavidha, okay,
okay Bapu's story [laughter] okay
Bapu's story, you are
good with the clothes
[laughter],
oh then [
laughter] no, you
[laughter],
room,
shop, you go
[laughter]
[screaming voice]
okay sir, okay, no sir, sir,
you
[laughter] no, no,
sir, your hard work has come to fruition,
sir, if
you refuse on the 13th,
okay, sir, it has come [laughter]
sir, namaskar, namaskar, namaskar, hey congratulations,
hey the government work
which is the lower
chairmanship
[laughter],
which select
dress
inconvenience dress, did not start, but from the expense of the
mari
[music] [song voice]
brother, did you
see the complete theft [laughter]
Bhabhi,
sand
[laughter]
P shirt P sh
[music]
I am
0, ho katha also [laughter] okay Babu
Chaturthi  Fourth
woman gets
up
[laughter]
Babu
Babu, tired
[music]
[music] Engineer
Hey Babu, you are facing
inconvenience
Babu, day by
day it is
good, good Babu,
work, good
sign, good sign, good sign, the
business is
going well, yes,
fine
in the innings [laughter]
[music]
good, good, yes, yes, good, good
Ganesh, good
[music]
work
Babu
[music]
[crying voice] Babu,
when will
Babu tell you, your
dress is home [crying voice] you are going to
dress
three yellow Babu,
today the dress is not a Muslim,
very bad Babu, Babu,
you prepare the Ganesh idol, whether it is a
Muslim or a Hindu, you know me,
Ganesh Thakur, I am a
Muslim, you
eat mutton, that is also a Muslim,
you eat it,
you give the money to the business,
Muslim, Hindu, Christian, Jain, Muslim,
Muslim, dress, you
worship, Babu,
look Babu,
who is a Muslim, Babu, but hey Muslim, hey
Muslim,
say hello Babu
brother, Allah Akbar
Akbar
brother Jagannath's
[music]
[music]  Pakh mud atak jaau [music] I am
going to Muruni
[music]
then after all [voice of singing] I have iron falling on me
[voice of singing]
maha
[music] I am happy, I know that even if I have
sorrow [music]
you are the landlord of the world,
you are the landlord [music] you are the world [music]
life [music]
you are the world
[music] if you
go then the
bell will eat the whole life [music]
Jai Shri Jagannath Jai Shri Jagannath
forgive me uncle, I have forgotten you
okay Baba okay okay let's go okay
[music] [voice of singing]
go to the place